{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/1202","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1202","name":"The Greek","address":"535 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Zina Karadimas","licenseNumber":"069263","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.04204,42.33537","geojson":{"id":"1202","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.042044509,42.335370275]},"properties":{"name":"The Greek","owner":"Zina Karadimas","address":"535 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"069263","establishmentid":"1202","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"26/4/2022"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4487","name":"Plaka Level 2","address":"535 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"389","name":"Golden Fleece Restaurant Inc.","address":"525 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622604","name":"Eat N Out Pizza & Gelato","address":"531 Monroe","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51623714","name":"Eat-N-Out Pizza & Gelato","address":"531 Monroe","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51623350","name":"Exodos","address":"529 Monroe Street ","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1488","name":"New Parthenon","address":"547 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1403","name":"Pizza Papalis Taverna","address":"553 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"388","name":"Pappy's Bar and Grill","address":"517 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2652","name":"Epiros Coffee House","address":"515 Monroe","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4270","name":"The Coffee House","address":"515 Monroe St.","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60508","inspectionDate":"2022-09-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelves","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"and the Ice machine","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"57475","inspectionDate":"2022-03-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"By the Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"55872","inspectionDate":"2021-09-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54261","inspectionDate":"2021-02-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"To prevent contamination of food or food related items","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"In the Storage shelves","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"and the Dry storage","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"52804","inspectionDate":"2020-09-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"and the Bar","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"and the Bar","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate."}]},{"inspectionid":"52200","inspectionDate":"2020-03-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49711","inspectionDate":"2019-11-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"At the SANITIZING","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the FRESH FRUIT","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Pop gun holsters","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"and the Bar","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2011-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"and the Dry storage","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"47758","inspectionDate":"2019-05-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Supv recurringLetter","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45979","inspectionDate":"2019-04-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"At the SANITIZING","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"and the Bar","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"The KITCHEN","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"and the Dry storage","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43604","inspectionDate":"2018-09-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41775","inspectionDate":"2018-02-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer bucket","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"At the SANITIZING","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"ACCESS","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"}]},{"inspectionid":"39552","inspectionDate":"2017-08-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"At the SANITIZING","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"window(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Screening that is sixteen mesh to the inch or greater","location":"OUTER DOOR(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"wet","problemDescription":"Stored in","subProblem":"Less than 50-100 ppm chlorine","location":"WIPING CLOTHS","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths in 50-100 ppm chlorine."},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Labels","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"39169","inspectionDate":"2017-07-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1202"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}